A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 84), 1963-1984; 1.10; 116.4 Cubic Feet; 97 standard record storage boxes - Box R2114-R2119, R2121-R2129. R2133-R2162, R2176-R2207, R2211-R2213. R2221-R2227 and R2230-R2239.
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - University Development - Education for Development Program - Gapjah Mada University (GMU), UD
      - General background on university development in Indonesia
      - Diaries of RF officers visiting GMU
      - Correspondence re RF policy on visiting faculty and personnel assigned to GMU
      - Correspondence from A.J. Nyberg re development at GMU
      - Correspondence re external assistance (non RF) to GMU
      - Correspondence re overall faculty development at GMU; overall library development; overall evaluations of allocations; personnel assigned to GMU
      - Program review documents
      - News clippings re social, economic and political developments in Indonesia
      - Program and policy issues at GMU which involve RF role and funding
      - Monthly reports of activities from RF representative, JE Black, 1981-83
      - Final report "EFD - cooperative program, GMU and RF, 1971-83
      Administration
      - Correspondence and memoranda on administrative matters concerning the operation of the EFD program center office, i.e. routine correspondence about officer and team visits (itineraries, travel arrangements, appointments) - to and from RF representative, A.J. Nyberg, and acting representative, R. Northrup
      - Correspondence and notification about bank deposits; audits; budgets and accountings: charges to local EFD center budget (see Note 1 below)
      - Personnel policies for local staff
      - Correspondence about starting at English speaking school in Yogykarta
      - Correspondence with field staff concerning articles and books which are of interest to them
      - Correspondence about the purchase of books and journals for RF staff members
      Note: 1) Correspondence and memoranda related to and charged to items shown in EFD center budget (attached) should be filed in 652 UD - Administration, with the exception of cars and housing.
      2) Correspondence re housing: SEE 652 UD - Gadjah Mada University - Staff Housing
      3) Correspondence re autos: SEE 652 UD - Administration - Automobiles
      Administration Automobiles
      - Correspondence, memoranda concerning purchase and shipment of vehicles for RF staff assigned to GMU
      Agreement
      - Correspondence, memoranda concerning RF agreement with Government of the Republic of Indonesia
      Agricultural Sciences
      - Correspondence and memoranda about AS interests at GMU; with AS field staff assigned to GMU. Correspondence dealing with the establishment and maintenance of relationships with agro complex at GMU
      - General correspondence about RF agricultural sciences fellows from GMU
      - Diaries of RF staff assigned to GMU (Tillman and Thompson, Crowder and Warwick)
      - Reports and papers on AS subjects in relation to curriculum development
      - Occasional "situation" reports vis a vis agro complex at GMU
      - Report by Tillman (December 1980) of seven year experience in EFD at GMU
      Medical Sciences (or Health Sciences)
      - Correspondence, memoranda and diaries of Lucien Gregg and Joe Wray concerning possibilities for an RF role in medicine and health related areas at GMU
      - Correspondence re development of a medical team at GMU
      - Reports of consultants assigned to investigate medical and health departments and facilities at GMU
      - Correspondence and memoranda to and from Jon Rohde and Robert Northrup on medical and health related issues, programs and policies
      - Sundry mimeographed project studies on comprehensive community health, population studies, child health
      Social Sciences
      - Diaries of K.W. Thompson and social science officers concerning an SS role at GMU
      - Correspondence and memoranda to and from D. Hedley and C. MacAndrews on general social science related issues, programs and policies
      - Because of A.J. Nyberg's role as RF representative and economics professor at GMU, 652 UD and 652 UD - Administration should also be consulted for possible social science related correspondence
      - Diaries of D. Hedley and C. MacAndrews
      Allocations and Fellows
      Individual files are maintained for each allocation (see 652 UD - Minutes for mark up) and for each Indonesian fellow (652 E)
      - (Indonesia - University development) (Minutes) (supplementary material), 1967 1969-1983 (Box R2126)
      - Administration, 1972-1984 (Box R2127)
      - Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box R2127)
      - Agricultural Sciences, 1980-1983 (Box R2127)
      - Agricultural Sciences, 1968-1979 (Box R2128)
      - Gadjah Mada University - Computer, 1975-1982 (Box R2237)
      - Gadjah Mada University - English language training, 19[??] (Box R2237)
      - Medical Sciences, 1968-1981 1983 (Box R2129)
      - Program Review, 1974-1975, 1977-1978 (Box R2129)
      - Program Review (supplementary material), 1979 (Box R2129)
      - Social Sciences, 1968-1971, 1974, 1976-1979 (Box R2129)
  - Greece, 749
    - Greece - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute - Small farmers, 1979-1983 (Box R2238)
  - Norway, 767
    - Norway - Medical Sciences, A
      - Bentsen, Bent Guttorm, 1981-1983 (Box R2238)
  - Portugal, 773
    - Portugal - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Pego, Silas E., 1977-1982 1984 (Box R2238)
  - 779
    - 779 - Social Sciences, S
      - Foreign Affairs (Ministry of) - Books, 1977-1982 (Box R2238)
  - Turkey, 805
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Hazar, Necati, 1979-1982 (Box R2238)
      - Kanbertay, Mesut, 1979-1982 (Box R2238)
      - Kinaci, Engin, 1979-1982 (Box R2238)
    - Turkey - Social Science, S
      - Hacettepe University - Child labor, 1977-1981 (Box R2238)
  - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries, 850
    - (Management Training Programs in Developing Countries), 1976- (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - International Organizations, 103
      - Panafrican Institute for Development - Management training, 1975-1984 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Massachusetts, 224
      - Paul, Samuel, 1978-1982 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Dominican Republic, 335
      - Asociación para el Desarrollo - Agricultural management training, 1978-1981 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Tanzania, 723
      - Eastern and Southern African Management Institute - Women in development, 1981-1983 (Box R2239)
    - Management Training Programs in Developing Countries - Turkey, 805
      - Bogazici University - Agricultural public management, 1977-1983 (Box R2239)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 85), 1970-1985; 1.11; 74.4 Cubic Feet; 62 standard record storage boxes - Box R2242-R2302 and R2304.
  Files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1985.
  - CIAT, 110
    - Blast resistance, 1980-1984 (Box R2242)
  - ICIPE, 117
    - Tick immunology, 1978-1980 (Box R2242)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Adolescent Fertility Regulation - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2242)
    - Antiparasitic Drugs - Conference (also (A 8[? ]), 1982-1984 (Box R2242)
    - Behavioral Epidemiology - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Deterrence Strategy & Psychology - Conference, 1983 (Box R2243)
    - Drama Exchange - Conference, 1983-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Education for Development Review - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2243)
    - Energy Protein Intake & Activity - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Foreign Debtors Default - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Human Error - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Infection Processes of Fungi - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2243)
    - International Comparison of Cancer-Causing Substances - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - International Network of Food Data Systems - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Italian - American Graduate Education - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Italian Institutions Performance - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Leprosy Research - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R2243)
    - Multinational Enterprises - Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2243)
    - NATO and the Mediterranean - Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Nitrogen Fixing Tree Association - Germplasm Conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Psychophysiology - Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2243)
    - Regional Security Arrangement in the 1980's - Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2243)
    - Scholars - Adamolekun, 1981-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Avineri, 1980-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bailyn, B., 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bailyn, L., 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Barrass, 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Barrett, F., 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bateson, 1981-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Beard, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Beck, R., 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bell, D., 1979 1981-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Brief, T., 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Bruce-Chwatt, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Cizmar, 1982-1985 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Craddock, 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Davies, 1981-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Del Tredici, 1980 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Desowitz, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Diggins, 1982-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Dolzer, 1982-1984 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Dunajewski, 1981-1983 1985 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Elshtain, 1980-1983 (Box R2244)
    - Scholars - Flaherty, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Frankel, 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Freeman, J., 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Ghent, H. (did not go), 1979-1981 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Godman, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Goldberg, H., 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Haskel, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Heady, 1982-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Horowitz (did not go), 1981-1982 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Humphries (& Barbieri), 1981-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Jackson, W.A.D., 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Jerison, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Jonsen, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kellerman, 1983-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - King, 1978-1980 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kolko, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kraehe, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Kuhn, 1982-1984 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Lambert, 1981-1983 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Lelyveld (did not go), 1979 (Box R2245)
    - Scholars - Leon, Carlos A., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Lewis, Richard W.B., 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - McMillan, Carl H., 1981-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - McPhee, John a., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Malamud, Bernard, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Martin, Jay, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Marx, Leo, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Mayor, Heather D., 1979-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Miedzyrzecki, A., 1981-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Miles, Margaret R., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Minear, Paul S., 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Nowotny, Thomas, 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Oakes, Rodney, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Peden, Margaret S., 1981-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Perlman, Mark, 1981-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Perlongo, Daniel J., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Robinson, Kenneth L., 1982-1983 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Rostow, Walt Whitman, 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Rowley, Charles D., 1982-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Ruttan, Vernon W., 1980-1984 (Box R2246)
    - Scholars - Saward, Ernest W., 1981-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Scanlan, James P., 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Schoultz, Lars, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Segre, Dan Victor, 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Shaffer, Richard, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Siegmeister, Elie, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Silver, George A., 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Sinclair, Sir Ian, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Singer, Jerome L., 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Stone, Robert, 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Stryk, Lucien, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Swing, John T., 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Thurston, H. David, 1981-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Treitler, Leo, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Uttal, William R., 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Wang, In Kuen, 1981-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - White, Robert E., 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Witte, Ann Dryen, 1982-1983 1985 (Box R2247)
    - Scholars - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Selective Primary Health Care - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Sorghum Diseases Conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2247)
    - Stability in South and Southeast Asia - Conference, 1981-1982 (Box R2247)
    - State Power in China Conference, 1980-1983 (Box R2247)
    - Survey Research in Arab World Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2248)
    - War and Society in East Central Europe - Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Welfare State: Dangers for Women Conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2248)
  - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy, 150
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Connecticut, 208
      - Olsen, Randall J., 1980-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Louisiana, 221
      - Newman, John, 1980-1984 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Massachusetts, 224
      - Repetto, Robert, 1980-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Missouri, 228
      - Hicks, W. Whitney, 1980-1984 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Rhode Island, 244
      - Fosu, Gabriel Basil, 1981-1983 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Wisconsin, 255
      - Palloni, A., 1981-1984 (Box R2248)
    - Social Science and Legal Research on Population Policy - Peru, 331
      - Universidad Peruana Cayetano Heredia - Mortality differentials conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2249)
  - Demographic Evaluation Projects, 151
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Michigan, 225
      - University of Michigan - Mexican migration to United States, 1980-1983 (Box R2249)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Colombia, 311
      - Corporación Centro Regional de Población - Demography, 1978 1981-1984 (Box R2249)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - 724, 724
      - Chilivumbo, Alifeyo, 1981-1983 (Box R2249)
    - Demographic Evaluation Projects - Liberia, 759
      - University of Liberia - Fertility regulation, 1981-1982 (Box R2249)
  - CILCA, 165
    - (Food Corps Programs), 1978-1983 (Box R2256)
  - 172
    - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Antifertility peptides, 1982-1983 (Box R2256)
    - Chinese Academy of Sciences - Reproductive endocrinology (also 6[unreadable]), 1981-1984 (Box R2256)
    - National Institute of Nutrition Salvador Zubirán - FSH microheterogeneity, 1983-1985 (Box R2257)
    - University of Ibadan - Membrane physiology, 1980-1983 (Box R2257)
    - University of Lagos - Gonadotropin, 1980-1983 (Box R2257)
  - 175
    - 175 - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Allen, Walter R., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Blake, John H., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Brown, Frank, 1979-1982 (Box R2257)
      - Camarillo, Albert, 1982-1983 (Box R2257)
      - Champagne, Duane, 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Cole, Lorraine T., 1981-1984 (Box R2257)
      - De la Garza, Rudolfo O., 1979-1982 (Box R2257)
      - Dong, Lorraine, 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Fry, Gladys-Marie, 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Hare, Bruce R., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Jefferson, Francine E., 1982-1983 (Box R2257)
      - McLemore, Leslie B., 1982-1984 (Box R2257)
      - Myers, Samuel L., Jr, 1979-1980 (Box R2257)
      - Neighbors, Harold W., 1981-1983 (Box R2257)
      - Ruiz, Richard, 1982-1985 (Box R2258)
      - Sanchez, Marta, 1982-1983 (Box R2258)
      - Simpson, Gwyned, 1981-1984 (Box R2258)
      - Stall worth, Lamont E., 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
      - Stanfield, John H. II, 1981-1983 (Box R2258)
      - Sue, Stanley, 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
      - Walton, Hanes, Jr., 1979-1982 (Box R2258)
      - Wilkerson, Margaret, 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
  - U.S. Immigration and Refugee Project, 181
    - Fagen, Patricia Weiss, 1982-1985 (Box R2258)
    - Reimers, David, 1982-1984 (Box R2258)
  - Utilization of Fragile Environments and Marginal Lands, 190
    - National Agricultural Research Institute - Valverde S., Carlos, 1980-1984 (Box R2258)
    - North Carolina State University - Perry, Jesse, 1978-1983 (Box R2259)
    - Utilization of Fragile Environments and Marginal Lands - CIAT, 110
      - Amazon Basin, 1981 1983-1984 (Box R2259)
  - 195
    - International Training & Research in Clinical Epidemiology (file appears to be incomplete), 1980 (Box R2259)
    - Shanghai First Medical College - Health Records, 1980-1983 (Box R2259)
  - 199
    - Beacon Hill Research Foundation - Gossypol, 1982-1984 (Box R2259)
    - Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences - Gossypol acetic acid, 1981-1983 (Box R2259)
    - Population Council - Gossypol, 1981-1983 (Box R2259)
    - University of Michigan - Gossypol, 1981-1984 (Box R2259)
  - United States, 200
    - Agricultural Development Council - Social Science, 1982-1984 (Box R2259)
    - American Assembly - American Political Parties Conference, 1981-1984 (Box R2259)
    - Atlanta University Center - Planning and development, 1979-1983 (Box R2259)
    - Brookings Institution - Voluntary sector, 1982-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Citizen's Committee for Immigration Reform, 1981-1984 (Box R2260)
    - City University of New York - Summer high school program, 1982-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Columbia University - Women and income in the third world conference, 1981-1983 (Box R2260)
    - Denver - Education - Administrative interns, 1975-1980 (Box R2260)
    - Equity Policy Center - Women's roles on small farms conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Flexner, James T., 1979-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Harvard University - Intergenerational mobility, 1980-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Howard University - Development officers training, 1979-1981 (Box R2260)
    - International Fertilizer Development Center - Hansen, 1980-1984 (Box R2260)
    - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law - Mississippi interns, 1973-1981 1983 (Box R2261)
    - Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights Under Law - North Carolina municipal services, 1979-198[?] (Box R2261)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - International nutrition center, 1972-1984 (Box R2261)
    - Memphis - Education - Leadership development, 1974-1981 (Box R2261)
    - Mexican American Cultural Center - Youth leadership, 1981-1984 (Box R2261)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund - Voter law policy, 1980-1984 (Box R2261)
    - Millsaps College - Mississippi Freedom summer anniversary, 1979-1980 (Box R2262)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - Voter registration, 1982-1985 (Box R2262)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - Voting law, 1980-1984 (Box R2262)
    - National Association for the Southern Poor, 1976-1984 (Box R2262)
    - National Congress of American-Indians - Textbooks, 1981-1984 (Box R2262)
    - National Council on Crime and Delinquency - Community crime prevention, 1982-1983 1991 (Box R2262)
    - National Executive Service Corps, 1978-1984 (Box R2263)
    - National Institute for Work and Learning - Fast food industry and employment, 1981-1984 1991 (Box R2263)
    - Notional Puerto Rican Coalition, Inc. - [unreadable], 1981-1984 (Box R2263)
    - National Urban League - Busing/school desegregation conference, 1982-1983 (Box R2263)
    - New York University - Law internships, 1978-1981 (Box R2263)
    - Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund - Voting rights, 1982-1983 (Box R2263)
    - Rockefeller University - "Sharp compassion", 1980-1983 (Box R2263)
    - Southern Education Foundation - Black colleges, 1979-1981 1984 (Box R2264)
    - Southern Regional Council - Voting rights, 1980-1984 (Box R2264)
    - Southwest Voter Registration Education Project - Chicano survey, 1980-1984 (Box R2264)
    - University of Chicago - Foundations and public policy, 1977-1982 (Box R2264)
    - University of Florida - Agriculture, change and human values conference, 1982-1984 (Box R2264)
    - University of Notre Dame - Hesburgh papers, 1982 (Box R2264)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Black law journal, 1981 (Box R2264)
    - University of South Alabama - At large election procedures, 1981-1983 (Box R2265)
    - University of Virginia - Law of the sea, 1978-1982 1984 (Box R2265)
    - University of Wisconsin - Cross national disability policy study, 1981-1984 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Employment affirmative action, 1981-1983 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Job seekers and openings, 1981-1984 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Minorities and women federal employment, 1981-1984 (Box R2265)
    - Urban Institute - Women's lifetime earnings, 1983-1984 (Box R2266)
    - Virginia State College - Public administration training, 1975-1985 (Box R2266)
    - Voter Education Project, Inc. - Conferences, 1981-1984 (Box R2266)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Beth Israel Hospital, Boston - Bibliographies retrievals, 1982 1984 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Akhter, 1980-1984 (Box R2266)
      - Center for disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Huezo Toledo, 1980-1983 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Disease Control - Family planning evaluation - Moses, 1981-1983 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Public Resources, Inc. - Tropical disease, 1980-1982 (Box R2266)
      - Center for Public Resources, Inc. - Tropical disease & suppl. material, 1978-1979 (Box R2267)
      - Columbia University - Family planning training, 1979-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Cornell University - Geographic medicine planning, 1978-1981 (Box R2268)
      - Ellner, Jerrold J., 1980-1985 (Box R2268)
      - Garcia-Blanco, Mariano A., 1982 1984 (Box R2268)
      - Harvard University - Walsh, Julia, 1980-1983 (Box R2263)
      - New York University - Biomedical research, 1982-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Pan American Health Organization - Regional medical library, 1979-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Rockefeller University - Leprosy, 1982-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Tufts University - Health indicators conference, 1979-1985 (Box R2268)
      - University of California - Metabolic pathways, San Francisco, 1981-1985 (Box R2268)
      - University of Hawaii - Vaccine, 1979-1984 (Box R2268)
      - University of Maryland - Growth of children, 1982-1984 (Box R2268)
      - Yale University - Ticks, 1980-1984 (Box R2269)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Agricultural Development Council - Panayotou, 1980-1984 (Box R2269)
      - Cornell University - Pest control, 1977-1982 (Box R2269)
      - Cornell University - Phytoalexins, 1977-1984 (Box R2269)
      - Harvard University - McPherson, 1981-1984 (Box R2269)
      - Kansas State University - Protoplasts, 1978-1983 (Box R2269)
      - Louisiana State University - Soil redox, 1980-1984 (Box R2269)